

STEFAN DE RAADT

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Phone: +31 6 8318 9996

E-mail: stefanderaadt@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://stefanderaadt.nl

ABOUT ME

My name is Stefan de Raadt, I'm 22 years old and I live in Maurik (Gelderland). In my spare time I like: gaming, hiking, sport fishing, skating and running. Furthermore, I like to discover the latest techniques/frameworks in the field of software.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Software Developer

NTR Dutch public-service broadcaster – Het Klokhuis (2019)

- Worked on the new Gamestudio, a web app that allows users to build their own games and share them with other users.
- Techniques: React.JS, Sass and Javascript (ES6)

Software Developer /Intern

Minox (2018 – present)

- Developed my internship assignment where I had to link ledger accounts to RGS (Reference General ledger Scheme). Because of this assignment its easier to connect and share data between ledger accounts in for example dashboards.
- Techniques: React.JS, Node.JS, Docker, Microservices and Javascript (ES6)

Software Developer Astecom (2016 – 2018) /Intern

- Final internship at: ROC A12. I was mainly busy with an unknown language: PxPlus. This internship made me much better at solving problems independently, mainly because of the lack of documentation/information about this language.
- Techniques: PxPlus, PHP, Laravel and React.JS

Intern TWS Media (2015)

- First internship in which I gained a lot of general programming knowledge. TWS Media was a company that mainly developed websites in Drupal.
- Techniques: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Drupal and Java

SKILLS

Languages

• Javascript (ES6/ES5), HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Java, Json, Node, JS, PHP, Ruby and C#.NET

Frameworks/Tools

React.JS, Vue.JS, Jest, JUnit, Git, Docker, Express.JS, Laravel, Spring Framework, Unity, Xamarin, Bootstrap, Bulma and Ruby on Rails

Other skills

Scrum, Test Driven Development and various Design Patterns

EDUCATION

HBO-ICT Software & Information Engineering

HU University of Applied Sciences Utrecht (2016 – present)

MBO 4 Software Development

ROC A12: Intermediate Vocational Education in Software Development (2013-2016)